http://www.safepasswd.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
SafePasswd.com ("SafePasswd.com") operates several websites including safepasswd.com.
It is SafePasswd.com's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, SafePasswd.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. SafePasswd.com's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how SafePasswd.com's visitors use its website. From time to time, SafePasswd.com may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
SafePasswd.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. SafePasswd.com does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to SafePasswd.com's websites choose to interact with SafePasswd.com in ways that require SafePasswd.com to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that SafePasswd.com gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who fill our our contact form at /contact to provide a name and email address. Those who engage in transactions with SafePasswd.com - by purchasing access to advanced features, for example - are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, SafePasswd.com collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with SafePasswd.com. SafePasswd.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Aggregated Statistics
SafePasswd.com may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, SafePasswd.com may monitor which password type is prefered by users, or the average length of password generated. SafePasswd.com may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, SafePasswd.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
SafePasswd.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on SafePasswd.com's behalf or to provide services available at SafePasswd.com's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using SafePasswd.com's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. SafePasswd.com will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, SafePasswd.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when SafePasswd.com believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of SafePasswd.com, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an SafePasswd.com website and have supplied your email address, SafePasswd.com may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with SafePasswd.com and our products. We primarily use our websites and blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. SafePasswd.com takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. SafePasswd.com uses cookies to help SafePasswd.com identify and track visitors, their usage of SafePasswd.com website, and their website access preferences. SafePasswd.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using SafePasswd.com's websites, with the drawback that certain features of SafePasswd.com's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, SafePasswd.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in SafePasswd.com's sole discretion. SafePasswd.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Home
About
Blog
Help
Developer API
Link To Us
Terms of Services
Privacy Policy
This service is provided "as is, as available" without warranty, express or implied.
Any use is at your own risk.
Like this site? Put a button on your site!
.
